Hello all I am Arnaud Paran Data scientist at the DataLab Groupe of Crédit Agricole in France and I am going to show you the work that we published at ICDAR 2023.
Machine learning is now used a lot for various document processing tasks.
However, we know that machine learning models are vulnerable towards adversarial attacks.
But, there is no litterature evaluating effectiveness of adversarial attacks on documentary data.
That's why we implemented various attacks on document classification models.
We showed that the models are at high risk of being attacked,
even when compressing the image, rendering it grayscale, being in a black box setting or even attacking a surrogate model.
That conclusion is highly concerning and we should all start evaluating robustness of our models.
However, we also showed that adversarial training makes our models robust towards adversarial attacks.
I wish that I will see you during ICDAR 2023 to tell you more about that work.